We would like to play together in Omotesando World!
Yay!
I wanted to see it.
No way!
That's amazing!
When did this happen?
I still don't remember.
Wow.
Come on.
Come on!
We're all passing each other.
I'm scared.
They're having fun.
Watch out!
Shouldn't there be a camera here?
I don't need it. I don't need it.
Denchanspill camera.
How do you do that?
Use a propeller?
We can go around. We can go around.
I wish we could go in circles.
That's what I'm talking about.
Please!
Wow, subtle.
I'll open it.
You can't open it, can you?
It's down there.
I got it.
But I don't have a card.
Go around this way.
Can you get in this way?
Yes, I can.
Go around this way.
You want it here?
I'm gonna stay here.
I'll take the slot.
If we go this way...
So this is how it's gonna work.
You want to slot in?
Born again
How about a seat in Ginza?
You can play in the wind, too. You're not going to lose money, are you?
I can play... 9 to 9, I'll go.
What? Just in case... this will increase your kakeki and reduce it.
How much do you want to spend?
Wow!
What a joke
150 million minutes already
I'll take it in and we'll spin it.
How's it going? How's it going?
Does it stop on its own?
Oh!
It's at the bottom.
I got it!
Yeah!
I should've played more.
I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it.
That's a little increase.
I can't do it.
I don't like that color.
I'm scared.
I don't know.
Up there?
Oh, no.
Oh, wait.
Oh, my God.
Look, look, look, there it is.
Oh, shit.
What? No, no, no.
Oh, isn't that good?
Oh, no.
But it'd be nice if we could swing next time and go around in circles.
You know, before we started, the staff asked me how bad I wanted to be.
So I'm going to be a bad person.
So I'm going to be bad.
See?
Just holding it.
Hmm.
I don't know.
Oh, my God!
What is this guy!
Ginji? Ginji? Ginji?
Wait, all of them? Maybe...
Oh, oh, oh, I'm glad it's not all of them.
It's crispy, but there's nothing in it.
Zero meat.
Skin.
Delicious
The iron's close, but...
The iron is close.
I don't know what to do.
It would be nice if we could go around in circles.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Let's use it.
Yes, please.
Yes, sir.
You want to go around?
This one's just off the edge.
Or it's stuck in the same spot.
Everywhere we go.
It keeps going in circles.
If it goes through the same place...
I don't know if it's stuck.
It sticks.
It sticks, doesn't it?
Yes.
I'll go around first, and then I'll decide what I want to do, and then I'll follow it as I like.
So it's up the street to the left.
Image...
Then I'll make a decision and go from there.
I know...
What shall we do?
What are we gonna do? Go someplace far away?
What do we do?
Go somewhere around here?
I was going to suck the rich man's money.
Here we go.
This way.
You wanna go up? Let's go up.
Yes, sir.
Oh, wow.
There's not many of them.
Yeah.
Don't go red again.
That's terrible.
If it's this way, I can't see it anymore.
What for?
You couldn't see it. We can't buy it.
We can't buy anything else.
No more cards, no more anything.
I can't buy anything more.
Just throw it away.
That's great.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, my God.
Is there such a thing as a nice drink?
The money's in the middle of the bottle.
Earth minus one.
Oh, my God. Is that okay?
It's great, but...
It's kind of boring.
I don't even have a card.
You're right, you're right, you're right.
It's kind of far away.
And money
My train is boring
My train is boring.
I've never seen that before!
I've never seen that before... and I've never seen that before... and I've never seen that before... and I've never seen that before...
There's no card with a "Grip" on it.
What?
Why? Why the Iron King?
That's not what I meant.
Oh, there's so many.
I don't get it.
What are we gonna do?
Hmm... the early route.
I like the card.
You want to go that way?
Let's go.
I ate the wizard.
I tried to get the wizard.
I'm going for the oranges.
Give it a shake.
I'm shaking it. I'm looking for a place to go.
I'll find a place to go.
I'm just going to go for it.
Wait for the bars to reach the finish line.
That's one way to go.
But, you know, aren't we the furthest away now?
Not the furthest.
Where are we going to look?
The whole map?
How are we gonna find it?
Like this one.
It's the furthest thing from here.
No, no, no, no, no.
We have to go as far as we can.
Yeah, that's right.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah.
Oh, so many.
Sixteen squares.
That's a lot.
What do we do now?
Card.
We're going to the cards?
Let's go.
I don't have a card.
The poop card.
If we put the poop card down, we won't be able to get it.
You won't be able to get it off.
You're right.
I have so many!
I'm kind of happy about it, but...
I have so many.
I'm not going back.
And I'll get you some clothes.
Daikon radishes are delicious.
Delicious radishes.
I can't afford them.
Oh, I'm back.
I'm back!
Oh, thank goodness!
The world has color again.
Minus 2.3 billion.
The other president at Wool.
That's so funny.
Wow.
Three.
That's not going anywhere.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
He's in the groove.
You're so close.
That's fun.
Happy trails.
I love it.
We're on the winning side.
Oh, man.
It's so far away.
Poo poo poo...
It's back with a poo poo poo.
It's Friday.
You want to use it?
Where? Where are we going?
Where was I?
We're doing a riff range.
But we're getting the iron... the iron?
Iron... iron... soon?
We're almost there.
Okay, well, just...
I don't want to get caught up.
We have a lot of it. We'll use it.
There's so much of it.
Don't tie me down.
I like that.
It's a normal success.
I hope you get a bomby for such a peaceful girl.
I'm scared, I'm scared
I don't want the girl I love
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
a. Tongzhou
I've got a special recard, and I'm going back to zero... I've got to pay up!
I've got it!
I'll be back in zero.
I'm a little close, so I can talk, but I'm whispering
I didn't write down the plan.
You're not talking at all.
This close? Here.
Yeah, it's close.
I see... I can't buy it.
It's so sad.
I guess you guys can afford it.
Oh, wait.
Oh, no.
What?
Oh, it's for the future.
Oh, yeah.
That's so sweet.
Mmm.
Boo-hoo!
That's terrible.
I thought I was gonna get something.
I've been here all day and I'm still not getting any "orao" from you.
I'm not getting any.
I'll use it up.
Great.
I'll go this way.
I want to go this way.
Lots of red.
So many reds.
So many cards.
But we're out of one.
Yes, you're right.
Here.
I want to go here.
This way?
Yeah, this way.
I have a billion dollars.
What do you want to do with it? Cards?
Look where it's going.
It's a players' field.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
What?
It's like a cathedral or something.
It'd be cool to buy one of those.
That's cool.
We're cool.
A cathedral.
There's a sightseeing tour.
Oh, my God, what are we gonna do?
We have money, we have credit cards...
He's talking through his nose.
Players' Square.
That's 800 million.
Or a regular card or something.
I'm sure.
Cards, you know, like DeBru and stuff.
What's an alpaca mania?
Do you eat alpacas?
You don't eat alpacas.
Do you make stuffed alpacas?
Stuffed alpacas?
Alpaca stuffed animal shop.
I'll get you a card.
I'm writing a card. I'm gonna use it.
I love it. I'm in. I'm in.
Oh, great.
I can't wait to get to the finish line.
Oh, it's gonna be a Bomby.
Bombie confirmed.
You can't buy cards, huh?
You can't buy a card, you get a card, you get a card.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good.
What? No way! That's just a little kid!
He's just a little boy.
Oh, no!
Why?
I'll lose my card!
Oh no, it's me!
It's you! It's Den-chan!
Oh, no... oh, no... oh, no... oh, no...
Oh, no.
How do you get two kings in a row like this?
What luck!
I mean, I was just about to say, "Oh, my God!" and then the one that changed to a little guy...
I'm tired of the king.
I'm tired of being in love with the King.
First love, first love.
first love... first love... first love...
First love, first love, first love...
Oh, he's playing with you. He's playing with you again.
I'm being played again. I'm being played. I'm being played.
He's playing with you. He's playing with you. He's got you in the palm of his hand.
Let's call it. Let's call it. It's us.
Let's call it. Let's call it.
You want to go get some?
Sure.
You mean all the money's gone, right?
That's right.
After all, I have to pay for it.
Just for looking for me.
It's like you're looking for me.
I'll be fine.
Oh, that's close.
So you're saying we can get as close as we want?
Yeah, we can make it. Let's go to the cards.
Let's go, let's go.
What about the other side of the world?
Brazil?
We're still alive.
Japan.
Oh, my God, he's an idiot.
Cute.
Catawas?
I like "kawaii baka.
It's the same in Japan.
Brazil?
Cute.
It's a kuno.
It might be my last card.
I'll take the money.
Next time, I'll take the iron umbrella.
That's right, he's mean, isn't he?
Like picking on the girl you like.
Sukira likes us so much...
I think she likes us so much. No, she's going to play with us and dump us.
We'll be played with and dumped.
What?
I'm afraid of footsteps.
They don't add up to anything.
Oh, no.
The card.
The card that got me out.
You gave it to me
Amnesia.
Wrong person.
Different person.
It's me, this time of night.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I just got off work.
Laughs
Oh, white.
I think I'm going to keep it.
You're going around...
What's going on? Don't call me "I"!
I'd appreciate it if you'd take it from me and buy it.
I thought you'd buy it from me.
What do you want?
The Iron King is playing with me!
I'm sorry. I'm starting to hate you.
That's zero yen!
Tetsuou!
I really like him!
That's great!
We're going to have some kind of company.
Company?
We talked about it.
Oh, my God! Sadness!
I'm sad!
It's going down.
It's my last year.
It's our last year.
We're falling in love with each other.
Oh, my God!
You're doing just fine.
Oh!
And, Bombie.
He's so cute!
He's smiling.
Isn't he great?
That's great.
Come on, man.
Come on.
Wow.
Oh, right.
Huh?
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Where are we?
I'd love to come by.
Please.
Where?
East Africa? Ethiopia?
Me too?
So close! Maybe just a little bit closer.
Closest.
King Mombee.
That's right.
Oh, man.
I've got to go for it.
You're right. I changed my face.
There's a lot of them out there.
He's on the move.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Scary!
High!
You look so cute doing nothing right now.
Cute?
You're so cute.
It's okay. It's okay.
We can buy a museum.
What are you gonna buy?
Why me? Why only one?
Oh, someone else has more than you.
Oh, yeah, me.
Chicken.
Chicken is cute.
It was my property with my friend.
Let's buy it.
What? They both have 400 million.
We can buy both of them.
3.2 billion.
But then we'd only have 200 million left.
What, buy a museum?
Buy a museum?
Wow.
Because you only have a year left.
Yeah, forever.
One more year.
That's what rich people do.
They buy museums.
You never say that in your life.
I've never said that before in my life.
Yay!
I'm buying a museum.
Oh, yeah, I don't have a card.
That sucks.
One more square?
One square left, a star... but I can't buy it.
I can't buy it
I'm going without.
Oh, no.
But...
Card, card, card
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go!
I love it.
They're gonna keep it.
What? Seven squares!
What? It's so close!
It's so close!
I got a miracle.
I wonder if I have to use this.
So steady, so steady.
It's too steady.
Okra stew. Stew.
Okra. We met again.
We matched again.
What, what, money?
Oh!
Wow. What?
You mean? That sucks.
Condolences?
Oh, condolences?
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
I shouldn't do that.
She said "condolences.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's so close.
Oh, no.
He said 31 squares.
It's just a card.
No, thank you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's not gonna change.
Cards?
I'll use it.
It's not on the back.
Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This way, right?
Red.
I don't like red.
Oh, no.
I don't know.
I have a lot of cards.
I mean, I have a lot of cards, but the color...
What is it?
It's like, "This isn't good enough.
I'll see what I can do.
I'll see if I can find it.
Well...
Pull an angel card.
I got it.
Over there.
That's all I get.
I appreciate it, but...
Oh...
He's not coming.
Six.
Well, it's a long road.
It's a long road.
What?
I just got robbed by a bombey.
Did I?
I don't remember.
What is it?
Good night.
I don't have it.
What if I don't?
Oh, shit.
Oh, no!
My bad!
Oh, shit!
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no!
Oh, I'm scared. I'm scared, Gorgonby.
Put them on.
I'm scared.
I don't want to say "life in the dumps.
Excuse me. You're being rude.
I've had my downfall. I've had my downfall.
I'm done. I'm done.
I love it, Angel.
I love it.
Oh, my God.
We could use that card.
It's the only way to go.
Where is it?
Oh, my God.
Jamestown's kind of cute.
It's cute.
Is it full of James?
James.
Where's your mommy?
I'm James.
James. James.
What month is it?
June.
Is it this way?
Yes, it is.
There it is.
It's close.
Close.
This way, too.
You can go.
We can go.
Oh!
Here, uh, but it's just there, right?
Hey, it's close.
Oh, it's so close.
So close. So close.
Please don't do that.
Oh, wow.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
Three more questions.
I think I can do three questions and three.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Good, good, good, good.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Good, good, good, good
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Oh, wow, wow, the country's totally different! It's on the clouds!
Cute! It's so cute! It's like, "Wow, we're at Mr. Lifong's!
Wow!
That's a negative.
Oh, uh, uh, uh, you're gonna make it Jello, right?
Thank you.
Okay, okay, okay. I got it, I got it, I got it.
Let's try this one more time.
If I finish first.
I'll come right up to you.
Where's the kid?
What? Doesn't that look like it's too far away?
Back side?
Maybe we can go around back.
Maybe we can go in the back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
I hope the iron doesn't do anything crazy.
What's next is the major card... Born to rain...
Another where
Another scary what do you mean pet?
I like the Star Doors...
Oh no, this is still going to be a doozy, and it's being manipulated, and someone's going to do it so that the house loses a little bit.
I'm not sure what you're talking about, but I'll tell you what I'm talking about.
I've always wanted to try it.
I'm going to the back side of the "hey, I'm going to the back side of the hey, I'm going to the back side of the hey, I'm going to the back side of the hey!
I'm not even a person under my feet!
I'll put it down one more time
Put your poo down, it'll go to the one you put here
Put your poo down once...
You can't go through here.
Put your poo down.
It's lighter.
So cute!
So cute.
Here.
Hey.
Which one is it?
But it's the only way.
This way or this way?
That's closer.
What do we do now?
You want a card?
Yeah.
Maybe we don't need it anymore.
Maybe I don't need it anymore.
And I dropped a little poop in there for a change.
I don't know, maybe I don't even need the prop anymore.
This is it.
It's so far away.
I wonder if we can make it to the other side of the world.
It'd be nice if we could
I hope so.
The other side of the world
You can't change it
You're not gonna change
Pretty colors.
It's pretty.
I've never seen it before.
Scary, scary, scary.
What do you mean?
I don't know who I'm going to choose.
God in heaven is right.
Okay!
Oh, my God, it's so, so, so full.
Oh, my God!
Please don't do that.
I don't get you, Tanaka-san.
How did you get so lucky?
I'm telling the truth!
Really?
I don't like it.
Oh, no, Tetsuzakura!
Gourmet!
When did I buy it? When did I buy it?
Oh, great!
Lucky... it's just on the other side...
Can we use this place?
No, I... I... I...
Once, once, once!
You're right.
Even on the back side...
Is it the ocean, because that's where we are.
Blue? Is that what it is?
Green.
Green? Isn't it right here?
No, I'm not green.
Yellow.
I'm close.
Okay.
I think I'm going to go to this camp.
Grass.
It's that close.
It's so close.
1.8 billion in money.
Oh, yeah.
I can buy you a card.
Don't you want it? Here.
No?
Excuse me, sir.
Hello.
A lot of people here.
Yes, I'm here.
Back - wow, I got mixed up for 4 minutes, I passed just under 2 yen
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Cute!
I'm in trouble
Hard lett Glas!
Oh!
Pla bonne!
Yes!
No way!
Is that possible?
Yes, it's possible.
This is really bad.
It's a big step, but it's a big step.
Oh, my God!
Aah!
The up and down type
Oh, that's too funny.
Your timing was terrible.
I just wanted to be happy for once.
That's funny.
My stomach hurts.
But it's coming back so fast!
Go!
Ooh!
Good!
But I can go like this.
What?
Oh, no! That's what happens now.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Poor me!
Poor me!
I'm so sad!
Oh, thank God, thank God!
Do you have more?
Here you go!
What is this place?
It's up to you.
Kiss.
What's up with that?
Stop it.
I'm in a lot of pain.
She's decided to go with Hazuki.
Didn't he just use his community card?
It said something about you deciding on Hazuki.
What's he doing?
Bomby's here.
Oh, that's why Bomby's here.
Oh, so we're going regional?
No, he's coming out.
Let's get out of here.
It's not working yet.
It's a mess.
It's a mess. It's a mess, really.
It's not gonna work.
All right. Anywhere's fine.
Good night.
Wait, Hazlett, where are you?
Hey, hey, hey, I'm going for a bike ride.
He's cute.
Listen to me.
She's on a bike.
He's so cute!
Oh, she's up there.
Yeah, but...
Where's Hazlett?
There she is.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Where are you going?
Do you want to buy or not?
I can buy it now.
Uh-huh.
You can take your time.
I'll put it on a credit card.
I've got 2.2 billion.
2.2 billion?
I'm gonna spend it.
You wanna go here?
Can you buy it?
We can buy it all.
Dog, let's drink slowly.
Let's go ask Bomby about it.
Okay, okay.
Haz, stop it.
Please don't.
Three hundred.
Pull me a good one.
Here we are.
Nothing else.
Oh, Japan?
Vivia?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
You do?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm pretty sure that's a 3.
YIN.
I'm so mad. I'm so mad.
That's not Libya, I've never seen that before.
I'll leave it to you.
Finally, finally, finally!
I have to give it to him. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no...
What card? Dimensional music.
Oh, dimensional music.
How do we get it to him? I don't know. But I'll give it to you when I use the card.
That makes sense.
I'll just jump as close as I can.
Wow, that's good.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
That's good.
Let's use it.
Let's give him the iron.
You're giving it to him?
Use it.
Giving up, losing weight.
Nyajika Gakkouounts
Ariake
Kowahara
Richards
What the hell?
Ah!
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Good, good, good.
But you got the money, right?
Enough to buy it.
Yeah, you can afford it.
44, that's a little far.
Yeah, it's a little far.
I didn't see anything.
I forgot.
I just did it.
I just pooped.
Can we go around back?
Let's see.
I'd like to try the back side.
I want to try it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I can do it.
It's a great place to fly.
That's what it looks like.
It's not like that.
It's not like it's flying or anything.
Where? I don't know where we're going.
Where are we going? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Here, here, here.
Where is it?
Oh, man, I think we're going someplace totally weird.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
We've gone too far.
No one has reached the finish line yet.
But we're too close.
One or four.
Oh, yeah.
That didn't take much.
One... no... one...
I'm only in this area
You're right. We've been in the desert.
12 more?
We're close.
Oh, no, no, no.
What do we do?
We don't have enough cards.
It'll be fun.
But we've got to do it.
All six.
Oh, here we go.
Well, well, well.
I'll take the shortest.
Red.
Oh, it's that way.
But here.
Yeah. - Okay.
Let's go.
I can get one, I can get one, I can get one.
I'm always buying.
It's nice to have money.
It's true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's great.
Ho ho ho.
Oh, come here...
I'm scared.
All right, all right, all right.
Squeek...
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Okay, okay, okay...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
I put it on... I put it on...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Oh, the only card in the kitchen.
Ouch, a little meat, a little sticky, no sticky...
It's not attached, it's not attached, it's just a misunderstanding, a misunderstanding...
Oh, it's off, it's off, it's off, I can't see it, I can't see it
I can't see it, I can't see it, I can't see it...
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
Oh, I kicked it. I kicked it.
I don't know, it smells a little...
Are you okay?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
It's okay.
Watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
There's something in there.
Seventy-four.
It's far away.
It's Churi Akamatsu.
Churyu Akamatsu.
I was planning to make up for it this past year.
I've been going back and forth to the same places.
And it's negative.
I had no choice but to buy another property.
You're going back, right?
Let's start over.
Let's start.
It's only a year away.
One more year.
I bought instant noodles.
The whole island?
I got the whole island.
There are so many moai!
You have to finish.
He used the goal.
You gotta score a goal.
You gotta score a goal!
Oh, my God.
Top of the pile.
Looks really good.
It's the kind with the propeller on the back.
It's so cute!
If it comes with a propeller, it's twice as good.
It's so good!
I've lost.
I lost.
I don't care if I get paid for the plate.
I'm so negative.
Teleport!
That's so cool!
Let's go through.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
Are you playing with me?
Are they playing with you?
I don't know.
I don't know if I'll stick around until it's over. I think I'm going to have to.
I don't know where I'm going to stay.
That's a plus.
Maybe I'll buy another place.
You want to look at some more properties?
I could buy.
Let's buy.
Let's buy, let's buy.
Let's buy, let's buy, let's buy.
Where do we start?
How many exclusives?
I'm in. I'm in. I'm in.
No way.
We don't have any properties.
We're good. We're good.
Eight squares.
We're almost there.
We don't need it.
But we're going around.
Round and round and round
But I'm swinging five jet cards
Four jet cards.
What about this?
Oh, that's a good one.
This one?
Can I just hold it?
Can I just keep it?
You don't have to use it.
You want to try this?
I don't think I'm going to get in, but if there's a game I can get in, I think I can get in.
You should see what's in here... oh, he's definitely coming.
Oh, my God!
No, no, no, no...
I'm sure he'll be here...
Patty, look here!
I'm working on it.
Ten cells?
Ten squares.
Wait, why didn't you just go back where you were?
We can make adjustments here.
All the way around.
Eight, seven.
Well, let's take a look at that one.
From here.
From here?
Which way?
The light.
Let's go around one more time.
Maybe one more time.
Why is the magnifying glass spinning?
Which way, which way, which way?
Which way is the light?
Mombin's here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, but is there one missing?
Oh, I'm missing one.
It's missing one.
But if you go back and look again, yes.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Go back, go back.
This way?
Press back.
Oh, press B.
Yeah. - Okay.
And back.
Oh.
And if you go down...
I can go.
I can't.
But...
But it can go, right?
Eight more squares.
Not yet.
What?
Why not?
Back again.
Go back one more time.
Ta-da!
This way?
I don't think we can go.
No, I can't.
I just want to go around one more time.
Can we go around one more time?
Oh, I see.
We should stop before one.
We can stop one before.
And down.
One ahead.
Aah!
I've already gone around.
Oh?
Wait a minute.
Oh, please.
What?
Please, please, please.
For the first time.
First time I've ever done this!
Who's that? Who?
Please, who is it?
Who's there?
He's cute.
Does she look nice?
Does it look kind of cute?
Heaven.
I'm scared of heaven.
The... the scattering... the scattering...
What? What do you mean?
What? What?
What? Isn't this so much cooler?
What? What do you mean?
Can I have it? Can I have it?
What do you mean?
What?
What? What?
What? You don't pay, they give it to us.
tee, it's like the Nikkei.
We'll slip it to you, it's far from the end of the game.
There's a grandmother reeking of green peppers, and there's a cloud of some kind of crete that we got.
What?
We've been going around in circles.
That's a first.
I don't like this.
Come on, come to us.
It's a long way.
It's a nice place.
Oh, my God.
You want to get out of the desert.
Yeah, I do.
I'm getting a little tired of this view.
Start with me.
I'll get closer.
But it's not like there's any overlap with the beams.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Oh, sure, I'll come closer
I see.
It's not that easy to pass by there.
Yes, sir
Yes, sir.
Parents Eat, Shopify, and Son
Depends on the monster
It's not that hard, is it?
I'm a barbarian.
Two turns, right?
It's two turns, but it's not good.
I'm going to the end of the line.
I want to get there.
I just want to get to the finish line.
Just one.
Mmm.
Five years.
You want to go buy some? Buy?
It's more fashionable to have a lot of properties.
Can you afford them all? Yeah.
Yeah!
I'm scared.
Oh, I'm gonna get something!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Forget about...
Oh, uh...
You forgot.
It's gone...
Just a little bit, just a little bit.
Then I'll finish and finish.
Please.
Two, please.
I'll take care of it.
Pleasantly.
Was it the same there?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That sounded really disturbing.
It's very unsettling, isn't it?
But here's the thing.
I wonder which is more interesting from a TV point of view.
Oh, you're right, you're right.
This one's better.
This way, nothing happens.
I see... I see.
Minus mass.
They say it's supposed to be funny.
Get along.
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
What this guy will do
Yeah, this guy.
The same?
The same? That's what it looks like.
Huh.
I kind of hate this one.
That's pretty bad.
There's a lot of money down there.
It's gone down a lot.
That's a lot of money.
Minus 24.
Oh, it's a cut.
Oh, no, no, no.
Go get the money.
No, no.
No, no, no.
Don't make me do it.
Don't make me do it, don't make me do it, don't make me do it.
Make 'em do it, make 'em do it, make 'em do it.
Don't make me do it, don't make me do it, don't make me do it!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
That's not right!
It's not Halao!
That's not happening!
Hey!
Hey, that's crazy!
Hey, that's not right!
That's not right!
That's crazy!
I want to tweet the god of poverty!
That's not what I'm talking about.
That's not good.
Not good.
Not better.
No, it's not.
I don't believe it.
Let's go home.
Shall we go home?
Shall we go?
I already opened it.
I'm a little disappointed in Tetsuo.
Disappointed.
I thought it was a serious match.
It was a cheat.
He was a cheat.
He's so cute.
He's riding a bear.
We're on a train called the Golden, and we don't have any money.
Are you out of the pink?
I'm in pink.
I just barely bought it.
You're right.
I bought a lot of gold.
Oh, my God.
This is fun.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
He's such a good character.
He's so cute.
Oh, the poop's glowing.
I'm glowing poop.
Gold.
There's so many characters.
Look.
Oh, wow!
So cute!
He's so cute.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yay!
That's great!
I'm so glad you beat me.
I got it!
Just a little bit at the end.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Good game.
That's a good match.
That was a close one.
We're not even close. We're not even close.
Not even close?
I don't think you're looking at it right.
Oh, my God!
That's the company, Utah.
We're good.
I'm not cut out for this.
So, the winners are the two from Kakimayu!
Yay!
How was it?
I mean, we were just shooting, but we were just playing.
I've only played Momo Tetsu once before, so I was a model for the second game, but...
I've only had one normal Momo Tetsu game, so I was a model for the second one, but I'm really good at booboo, and that was a lot of fun, so I'd like to play again.
I wonder how it went... I'm going to ask you guys if it was really not a good time...
I haven't laughed so hard in a long time!
It was like a home party
It was like a sleepover.
It was fun, fun, fun! I'm so glad you're here!
I'm glad you guys had a good time.
I don't have a card, I can't do anything, I don't have any money... but... it was fun to watch you guys.
I want to do it again.
I didn't expect that...
I felt sorry for her... she was amazing in so many ways... a few months... a miracle... and a lot of feelings combined...
I'm glad you're here... because if that had happened at home... I'd have wanted to show you.
I'm glad we're here, because I'm sure we'll do it again, but this time we'll pair up again, and who knows, maybe we'll even get to do it again!
I'm glad we're doing it again... but who's going to be the one to take pity on us?
I'm doing it because I'm doing it, because it's a game, and it was fun.
So that's it.
I had a lot of fun at Table 2 World. Let's do it again, just the four of us.
Please subscribe to our channel and rate us highly!
Bye bye!